(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
んらあああ
Nraaaa!
みんな おりゅ～？
Is everyone here?
なのなのなっ！
Nano-nano-na!
絶体忠誠♡なのら！
Absolute Loyalty♡Nanora!
お菓子の国のお姫様
The princess of the Sweets Kingdom
とびきりプリティな0歳児
A super pretty zero-year-old
ピアノだって弾けるんだし
I can even play the piano, you know
赤ちゃんじゃないのらよ！
I'm not a baby, nanora!
ワガママだって言うけれど
People say I'm selfish, but...
ルーナはお姫様なのだから
since Luna is a princess...
ルーナイト達も執事も
the LuKnights and even the butler...
いちいちうるさいのら！
are all so noisy about everything!
さあ ルーナイト達！
Now, my LuKnights!
準備はできたのら？
Are you ready?
出陣なのら～！
It's time to head out, nanora!
パフェもしゅわしゅわも 早く用意するのら！
Quickly prepare the parfaits and fizzy drinks!
あれもこれも食べたいのら！
I want to eat this and that and everything!
おいしいのはひとりじめ
The tasty treats are all for me
まずいのや苦いのは ルーナイト達に差し入れ！
I'll give the gross and bitter ones to the LuKnights!
チョコレートの噴水も
Chocolate fountains...
キャンディの首飾りも
and candy necklaces too...
素敵なのたくさんあるのら
there are so many wonderful things.
だからルーナのために 集めて来てね
So go and gather them all for Luna!
絶対 絶対 絶対 約束
Absolute, absolute, absolute promise!
なのなのな！
Nano-nano-na!
ぐるぐる＠まわる＠まわルーナ
Guru Guru @ Mawaru @ Mawa Luna
まわる まわる まわる まわルーナ
Spinning, spinning, spinning, Spin-Luna
まわる まわる まわる まわルーナ なのら！
Spinning, spinning, spinning, Spin-Luna, nanora!
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる回って もっと ぐるぐる ぐるぐる回って
Round and round, spin around more, round and round, spin around more
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる回って みんな ぐるぐる ぐるぐる回って
Round and round, spin around everyone, round and round, spin around everyone
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる回って もっと ぐるぐる ぐるぐる回って
Round and round, spin around more, round and round, spin around more
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる回って ずっと ぐるぐる ぐるぐる まわルーナ
Round and round, spinning forever, round and round, spinning Spin-Luna!
ぐるぐる 地球は
Round and round, the Earth...
回り始め 幾億年
...began spinning billions of years ago.
いつまでも このまま
Forever like this...
回る みんなに 幸せを...
...giving happiness to everyone who spins.
回り続ける まわルーナ
Continuing to spin, Spin-Luna!
ますますますます 社会が ぐるぐる
More and more, the world spins round and round...
ま～... あれ？
Wh... huh?
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる回って もっと ぐるぐる ぐるぐる回って
Round and round, spin around more, round and round, spin around more
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる回って みんな ぐるぐる ぐるぐる回って
Round and round, spin around everyone, round and round, spin around everyone
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる笑って もっと ぐるぐる ぐるぐる笑って
Round and round, smile more, round and round, smile more
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる踊って みんな ぐるぐる ぐるぐる踊って
Round and round, dance around everyone, round and round, dance around everyone
ぐるぐる ぐるぐる回って
Round and round, spin around!
もっと
More
ぐるぐるまわって
Spinning round and round
ル〜ナ
Lu~na
ぐるぐるまわるの
Spinning round and round
まわル〜ナ
Spinning Lu~na
やあ！
Yeah!
いつもおとぎ話のお姫様
Always a princess from a fairy tale,
みんなの輝くお月様
everyone's shining moon.
今日はお休みして
Resting today,
重たい王冠今は置いといて
setting aside the heavy crown for now.
どっちの私も好きになってくれますか？
Will you fall in love with both sides of me?
どっちも欲しいから まんなかにいたくなるの
Because I want both, I want to be in the center.
スニーカーとシャツに着替えて
Changing into sneakers and a shirt,
歩き出したんだ
I've started walking.
出発のアラームは新しい
The departure alarm is new,
私が鳴らしてあげる
and I'll ring it for you.
両腕をいっぱいにしても
Even with my arms full,
ぎゅっとしたい
I want to hold you tight.
この気持ち入らない
These feelings won't fit.
片っぽなんて選べない
I can't choose just one side.
迷ってるならまんなかなんだよ
If you're lost, it's the center.
まんがいの青春
Youth in full bloom,
まんぷくに摂取
a full stomach intake.
まてんりゅうせいぐん
Skyscraper meteor shower,
まんでび in heaven
Man-devi in heaven.
まんめん笑顔にして
With a full smile,
まんてんすぎる思い出
memories that are more than perfect.
まーまるーな Happy day!!
Mawa-Luna Happy day!!
愛のまんなかてん
At the center point of love,
プリンセスを忘れるくらい
so much you forget the princess.
胸まんたんにきゅんとしてみたい
I want to feel my heart full of "kyun."
どっちだってホントの私
Whichever it is, it's the real me.
瞬きしたら君のどまんなか
If you blink, I'll be in your center.
まんなかに重なるちてん
The point overlapping in the center.
まんなかで欲張るちてん
The point being greedy in the center.
まんなかのまんなかちてん
The center point of the center.
恋する女の子のいいとこ取りで
Taking the best of a girl in love,
照れ隠しと素顔の今 まんなかちてん
the point between shyness and my true face.
跪きなさい。
Kneel down.
汝、この城の扉を叩いたものよ。
Thou who has knocked on the gates of this castle.
誓いなさい。
Vow.
このルーナの盾となり矛となり、
To be the shield and spear for this Luna,
夜はぐっすり眠れるまで、
until you can sleep soundly at night,
共にあることを！
to be together!
捧げなさい！
Offer it up!
姫であるぞ！
I am the princess!
止まるな！
Don't stop!
紅茶のカップ かちゃかちゃ鳴らさないで えらい！
Don't clink your tea cup, well done!
スコーンだって 零さず綺麗に食べて すごい！
You ate the scone without spilling, amazing!
たまに王冠 どっちが前か間違っちゃうの かわいい！
I put my crown on backwards sometimes, cute!
通ってよし！ なのら！
You may pass! Nanora!
開城〜！
Open the gates~!
第一条！
Article 1!
誰よりルーナが好きな人！
The person who loves Luna more than anyone!
第二条！
Article 2!
シルクのお布団持ってきて！
Bring me a silk futon!
第三条！
Article 3!
三時のお茶会来れる人！
The person who can come to the 3 PM tea party!
守れなかったら即制裁！
If you can't keep them, immediate punishment!
分かってほしいのら
I want you to understand,
これも帝王学を学ぶため…
this is also for studying monarchism...
愛という名の教育なのら〜！
It's an education in the name of love!
守ってルーナイト 想ってくんないと
Protect me, Lu-Knight, or you'll have to think of me,
プロムナード ボイコット なのののら！
promenade boycott, nano-nora!
手の甲に忠誠 誓えるの？ チュッ
Can you swear loyalty on the back of my hand? *Kiss*
ガラスの靴 履かせてワルツ！
Let me wear the glass slippers and waltz!
守ってルーナイト かまってくんないと
Protect me, Lu-Knight, or you'll have to look after me.
ブラウニーにキャンディー どれだけあってもね
Brownies and candies, no matter how many there are,
君がいなきゃだめ みんな心して
it's no good without you. Everyone, take heed,
捧げなさい！ 姫であるぞ！
offer it up! I am the princess!
守ってルーナイト 想ってくんないと
Protect me, Lu-Knight, or you'll have to think of me,
プロムナード ボイコット なのののら！
promenade boycott, nano-nora!
永遠の忠誠 この指に チュッ
Eternal loyalty on this finger, *Kiss*
ガラスの靴 履かせてワルツ！
Let me wear the glass slippers and waltz!
守ってルーナイト かまってくんないと
Protect me, Lu-Knight, or you'll have to look after me.
ブラウニーにキャンディー どれだけあってもね
Brownies and candies, no matter how many there are,
君がいなきゃだめ みんな心して
it's no good without you. Everyone, take heed,
捧げなさい！ 姫であるぞ！
offer it up! I am the princess!
んな〜い！
Nnaa-i!
みんなおりょ〜！
Everyone, oryoo~!
ホロライブ4期生、姫森ルーナなのら〜！
Hololive 4th Gen, Himemori Luna nanora~!
今日はルーナの生誕祭ライブ！
Today is Luna's Birthday Festival Live!
いぇ〜い！
Yay~!
みんな来てくれてありがと〜！
Thank you all for coming~!
今日のハッシュタグはこちら！
Today's hashtag is this!
デデン！
Ta-da!
＃姫森ルーナ生誕ライブ2025
#HimemoriLunaBirthdayLive2025
これでいっぱいツイートしてください！
Please tweet a lot with this!
みんなー！うなたんのオリ曲メドレーどうだったー？
Everyone! How was Una-tan's original song medley?
可愛かったー？
Was it cute?
ふむふむ、ふむふむ。可愛い可愛い、分かってたのらー
Hmm-hmm. Cute, cute, I knew it!
そしてー、今日のステージ見てくださいー！
And then, please look at today's stage!
でででででーん！
Ta-da!
すげー！雲だらけ！
Wow! It's full of clouds!
あっちのさー
Over there...
この雲の向こう、何があるのらーかなー？
I wonder what's beyond these clouds?
みんな予想してみてー！
Everyone, try to guess!
そして、今日のライブテーマはー
And today's live theme is...
Luna RebirthDayです！
Luna RebirthDay!
どんな意味があるのか、さてさて？
What kind of meaning does it have? Well, well...
そして、待って、ルーナイトー！
And wait, Lu-Knights!
歌ってる時に、うなたん、大変身しました！
While I was singing, Una-tan underwent a big transformation!
みんな気づいてくれたのらー？
Did everyone notice?
100万人記念で、
For the 1 million subscriber milestone,
新モデルになりましたー！
I've got a new model!
わああー！
Waaa!
そして、ポルーナイトがー
And Polunaite...
なんと、うなたんに魔法かけてくれたのらーよねー
Actually applied magic to Una-tan, right?
ポルーナイトー、ありがー！ありがー！
Polunaite, thanks! Thanks!
姫！姫！おーい！姫ー！どこにいんのらー！
Hime! Hime! Hey! Hime! Where are you!
わあ！この雲の向こうにいますー！
Whoa! She's beyond the clouds!
そうなのらーねー
That's right.
ねーねー、新しい姿、どー？どー？どー？
Hey hey, how's the new look? How is it?
めっちゃ可愛いよー！
It's super cute!
えっ、本当ー？
Eh, really?
せっかくだから、姫の以前の姿を出して比較してみよう！
Since we're here, let's bring out Hime's old look and compare!
いいね、いいね、いいね！
Good idea, good, good!
おわー！どこどこ？ああ、光ってる！出た！
Whoa! Where, where? Ah, it's glowing! It's out!
出た！パネルが出そう！出た、出た、出たー！
It's out! The panel is coming out! It's out!
えー見て！どーお？
Look! How is it?
それでは、まずは、足元から見ていきましょう！はい！
Now then, first, let's look from the feet! Yes!
あ、そうそうそう。あ、姫さん、いい感じですよ、これ！
Ah, that's right. Ah, Hime-san, it looks good!
どーお？どーお？
How is it?
なんか、これ影の感じとか変わった？
Did the shadow feel change or something?
変わった？変わった、変わった？
Did it? Did it change?
あー！スカートとかパニエの感じ変わったね！
Ah! The skirt and pannier feel changed!
おー可愛いねー！
Oh, it's cute!
いい感じ、いい感じ？
Is it good, is it good?
あ待って！ここら辺とか待って！これ、加圧トレーニングの効果...
Ah wait! Wait around here! Isn't the effect of the kaatsu training...
出てるんじゃないの？
showing here?
えっ、出てる？出てる、うなたん、出てる？
Eh, is it? Is it showing, Una-tan?
最近、加圧トレーニングしてる？
Have you been doing kaatsu training lately?
やってるよー！パーソナルだけどなー！
I am! Though it's personal training!
あ、そうそう。後ろ向いて、後ろ後ろ！
Ah, right. Turn around, to the back, back!
えっ、後ろ？およ？
Eh, back? Oyo?
おわー！これこれ！見てこれ！髪の毛の揺れ！
Whoa! This, this! Look at this! The hair sway!
あと、シルエットか！これめっちゃいいじゃん！
And the silhouette! This is really good!
そそそそ、えへへ、えへへ。
Right right, ehehe, ehehe.
あと、そしてね、うなたんの手も見てほしいのらなー
And then, I want you to look at Una-tan's hands too.
わあ！おててが、まあ小さくて可愛いねー！
Wow! The hands are so small and cute!
いいでしょ？手相もいい感じなのらー
Right? The palm lines are also good.
手相！あ、手相ね！うん、えへへ。
Palm lines! Ah, palm lines! Yeah, ehehe.
あと、顔も見てー！
Also, look at my face!
あーお顔！
Ah, the face!
パネルと比べるのちょっと難しいんだけど...
It's a bit hard to compare with the panel, but...
斜めから見た時の、あ、フェイスラインとか変わったね！
When looking from an angle, the face line changed!
超可愛いじゃん！
You're super cute!
えへへ。パパありがとのー！
Ehehe. Thanks, Papa!
うん。まあ是非みんなもね、過去の3D配信と見比べてほしいのらなー
Yeah. Well, I definitely want everyone to compare it with past 3D streams.
ねえ、ポルー、ポルーナイト？質問があるののだけど...
Hey, Polu, Polunaite? I have a question...
そっちの雲の向こうってどうなってるのらー？
What's beyond those clouds over there?
舞踏会の会場あるよ。来る？
There's a ballroom venue. Want to come?
えっ、マジ？
Eh, really?
おいでよ！馬車ー！
Come on! Carriage!
えっ、ば、馬車ー！？
Eh, c-carriage!?
わあ、めっちゃ光ってるー！
Wow, it's glowing so much!
わわわわー！でけー！
Wawawawa! It's huge!
これ、ムーンギャラクシーの時、
This is the carriage from Moon Galaxy...
ステージにくっついてた馬車なのらよねー！
...that was attached to the stage, right!
というわけで姫、乗っちゃってください！
So, Hime, please get in!
乗れるの？乗るのののー！
I can ride it? I'm getting in!
うわー！すごーい！中も豪華なのらー！
Uwa! Amazing! The interior is also luxurious!
ちょっとここ座ってみるのらー。よいしょ。
I'll try sitting here. Yoisho.
ルーナたんの人形もあるのらねー！
There's even a Luna-tan doll!
すごーい！
Amazing!
姫ー、準備はOKですかー？
Hime, are you ready?
もちろーん！出発進行なのらなー！
Of course! Let's get moving!
よし、飛びますよー！
Alright, we're taking off!
いくぞー！
Let's go!
うわ！動いたー！
Uwa! It moved!
わあ、進むぞー！
Wow, we're moving!
すげー！この馬車飛んでるのらなー！
Wow! This carriage is flying!
よし、よいしょ。こっち見てみるのらー。うわー！
Alright, yoisho. Let's look this way. Uwa!
すごーい！星と雲がめちゃくちゃきれいなのらー！
Amazing! The stars and clouds are so beautiful!
わあ、眺め最高なのらねー！
Wow, the view is the best!
ガタンゴトン、揺らしてますわー。いいのらー。
Clatter-clatter, it's swaying. It's nice.
こっちからも見てみるのらねー。よいしょ、よいしょ。
Let's look from this side too. Yoisho, yoisho.
こっちもすごい！眺め最高ー！
This side is also amazing! The view is the best!
わあ、いい感じなのらなー！
Wow, it feels good!
高いなー、でもここ。
It's high up here, though.
てかポルーナイトさん、このまま進んだら...
By the way, Polunaite-san, if we keep going like this...
目の前のデッケェ雲とぶつかるのらけどさー
We're going to crash into that huge cloud...
大丈夫なのさー？
...is it going to be okay?
どうすんで？ 向こうが何も見えねえのなの
What should we do? I can't see anything ahead.
いや、ご安心ください
No, please rest assured.
このポルナイトにお任せあれ
Leave it to this Polknight.
姫、少々揺れますぞ
Princess, it will shake a bit.
大丈夫？ つかまってて下さい
Are you okay? Please hold on.
あ、え、大丈夫これ本当に！
Ah, wait, is this really okay!?
困った！ 本当に大丈夫？
I'm in trouble! Is it really okay?
やばいって何なの、雲来てるよ！
This is bad! Clouds are coming!
わ、わ、もう帰れ！
Wa, wa, go back already!
うわあああああ！
Uwaaaaa!
あたし今最上級に可愛いの
I'm at my cutest now!
君に振られて
Being dumped by you
最上級に可愛いの
I'm at my cutest now
これが乙女の逆襲だ!
This is a maiden's counterattack!
もう気づいてるかもしれないけど
I'm sure you already realized, but...
言うわ
I'll say it
あたしね
You know...
今とても かわいい
I'm just so cute right now
君が始めた恋
The love you started
君が終わらすなんて
Why are you the one ending it?
何だそれ
What's that?
泣いちゃうぞ
I'm gonna cry, you know
かわいい
Cute
あたしの連絡だけ
I heard that just my messages...
通知OFFにしてたなんて
...were the only ones you turned off notifications for
友達から聞いたよ
I heard it from a friend
連絡しすぎたって
Saying I contacted you too much...
君が不安にさせるからじゃん
...it's because you made me insecure!
もう気にしてないけど
I don't care anymore
だって今...
Because now...
君に振られて
Being dumped by you
最上級に可愛いの
I'm at my cutest now
自分史上1番ときめき放つわ
I'll radiate the most excitement in my history
最上級に可愛いの
I'm at my cutest now
認めなよ
Admit it
乙女の逆襲だ!
This is a maiden's counterattack!
さすがに
As expected...
失恋直後は
...immediately after a heartbreak
涙でぐちゃぐちゃで
Being a mess from tears
かわいい
Is cute
君が泣かせたのに
Even though you were the one who made me cry
雑なサヨナラだった
Your goodbye was so half-hearted
何だそれ
What's that?
泣いちゃうぞ
I'm gonna cry, you know
かわいい
Cute
二人しか知らないって
That "only we two know" thing...
言ってた話だって
...that we talked about
どうしてあの子も知ってるの
How does that girl know it too?
別れてよかったなんて
Thinking "I'm glad we broke up"...
思わせないでほしかった
...I didn't want you to make me feel that way
好きだったから
Because I loved you
君に振られて
Being dumped by you
最上級に可愛くなりました
I've become the most beautiful I've ever been
君に振られて
Being dumped by you
最上級に可愛くなりました
I've become the most beautiful I've ever been
むしろありがと
Actually, thank you
最上級に可愛くなったって
That I've become the most beautiful...
ねえ
Hey
言って
Say it
知って
Know it
あいつがなんか可愛くなったって
That she's somehow become cute
ねえ
Hey
聞いて
Listen
君に振られて
Being dumped by you
最上級に可愛いの
I'm at my cutest now
自分史上1番ときめき放つわ
I'll radiate the most excitement in my history
最上級に可愛いの
I'm at my cutest now
認めなよ
Admit it
乙女の逆襲だ!
This is a maiden's counterattack!
最上級に可愛いの
I'm at my cutest now
君に振られて
Being dumped by you
最上級に可愛いの
I'm at my cutest now
あたしひたむきシンデレラ!
I'm a dedicated Cinderella!
退屈な月曜日
Boring Monday
あなたの香りで目覚めるの
I wake up to your scent
纏ったトップノート
Wearing my top note
そうよ 秘密の物語なの
Yes, it's a secret story
うまくリプライできない
I can't reply well
震えるハート
Trembling heart
ためらい×はじらい=空回り...
Hesitation x shyness = spinning in circles...
誘うファンタジー 重なっちゃうくらい
Inviting fantasy, to the point of overlapping
一途だもん
I'm single-minded
あなたに夢中...
I'm crazy about you...
Ah バズっちゃバズっちゃやぁだ!
Ah, Buzzuccha Buzzuccha, no way!
ねえ かまってかまって もっと!
Hey, pay attention, pay attention more!
誰もがあなたを狙っちゃう
Everyone's aiming for you
ウインク一つでメロメロにさせちゃって
Making them fall head over heels with just one wink
こっちの気も知らないで もう!
Without even knowing how I feel, jeez!
バズっちゃバズっちゃやぁだ!
Buzzuccha Buzzuccha, no way!
ねえ 射抜いて射抜いて ずっと!
Hey, shoot through me, shoot through me, always!
いつでもあなたに本気中
I'm always serious about you
誰よりあなたの特別でありたいの
I want to be more special to you than anyone else
誰よりあなたのトクベツでいたいの
I want to be your most special person of all.
あたしひたむきシンデレラ！
I'm a dedicated Cinderella!
どんな道が待ってても
No matter what road awaits me,
ガラスのヒールで駆けてくよ
I'll run through it in glass heels.
魔法が解けても醒めない夢を
A dream that never ends, even if the magic breaks,
あなたにあげるわ
I'll give it to you.
だから絶対 負けない！
So I definitely won't lose!
弱気お断り
No room for cowardice.
純愛したい まっすぐに
I want a pure love, straight and true.
想うエンパシー 伝わっちゃうくらい
An empathy so strong it's transmitted,
本気だもん
I'm serious, after all.
まさしく無敵ですっ
I'm truly invincible!
Ah ハマってハマっていいよ
Ah, it's okay to fall for me, fall for me.
ねえ ディグってディグってギュンと
Hey, dig me, dig me, until your heart thumps.
恋する乙女は変幻自在
A girl in love is ever-changing.
「キレイ」も「キューティー」も欲張りに励めば
Striving for both 'beauty' and 'cuteness' greedily,
輝く自分になるの
I'll become a radiant version of myself.
さあ！ ハマってハマっていいよ
Come on! It's okay to fall for me, fall for me.
ねえ 気づいて気づいてちゃんと
Hey, notice me, notice me properly.
まだまだ乙女は日進月歩
A girl is still making steady progress.
世界で一番のドキドキがほしいの
I want the world's greatest heart-pounding moment.
あなただけへのプリンセスですっ
I'm a princess just for you!
Ah 「好き」って「好き」ってなんで
Ah, why is it that saying 'I love you'...
そう ズキってズキって言うの
...makes my heart throb and ache?
けなげなココロは困惑中
My brave heart is currently confused.
愛しさ膨らんでこんなにも苦しいの
My love swells up and it's so painful.
今すぐこっちに微笑んで
Please smile at me right now.
Ah バズっちゃバズっちゃやぁだ
Ah, I don't want it to go viral, go viral.
ねえ かまってかまってもっと
Hey, pay attention to me, more and more.
誰もがあなたを狙っちゃう
Everyone will be after you.
ウインクひとつでメロメロにさせちゃって
Making them head over heels with a single wink,
ボクの気持ちも知らないで！
...while you don't even know my feelings!
もー！ バズっちゃバズっちゃやぁだ
Jeez! I don't want it to go viral, go viral.
ねえ 射抜いて射抜いてずっと
Hey, shoot through my heart, always.
いつでもあなたに翻弄中
I'm always being toyed with by you.
誰よりあなたのトクベツでいたいの
I want to be your most special person of all.
わがまますぎかな 許してね
Is that too selfish? Please forgive me.
あたしひたむきシンデレラ！
I'm a dedicated Cinderella!
オトメロディー
Oto Melody
スキスキスー フワフワフー
Suki-suki-su, Fuwa-fuwa-fu
こんなキモチ メロメロディ
This feeling is Mero-merody
夢だけど 夢じゃない
It's a dream, but it's not a dream.
お願いね マイメロディ
Please, My Melody.
オトナじゃない オトメです。
I'm not an adult, I'm a maiden.
恋するのが仕事です
Being in love is my job.
君の名前つぶやくと ドキドキするの
When I mutter your name, my heart pounds.
聞き分けない この胸が
This heart of mine won't listen,
歌い出して止まらない
it starts singing and won't stop.
上手じゃなくてゴメンナサイ
I'm sorry I'm not very good at it.
だけど聞いて とどけ
But please listen, let it reach you.
マイメロディ マイメロディ
My Melody, My Melody.
星空を越えて 君の夢 守るリボン
Across the starry sky, a ribbon to protect your dreams.
マイメロディ ハート見つけたなら
My Melody, if I find your heart,
グルグル巻きしちゃうからね
I'll wrap it up tight.
Wow wow wo 覚悟しといて
Wow wow wo, be prepared.
嘘じゃない
It's not a lie.
オトナじゃない オトメです。
I'm not an adult, I'm a maiden.
泣いたりだってしちゃいます
I even end up crying sometimes.
女の子って魔法で 作られたの
Girls were created from magic.
スキスキスー フワフワフー
Suki-suki-su, Fuwa-fuwa-fu
こんなキモチ メロメロディ
This feeling is Mero-merody
夢だけど 夢じゃない
It's a dream, but it's not a dream.
お願いね マイメロディ
Please, My Melody.
キライじゃない ってゆーかスキ
I don't hate you, I mean, I love you.
スナオになんてなれません
I just can't be honest.
君の笑顔見るだけで フニャフニャするの
Just seeing your smile makes me go all weak.
それなのにー それなのに！
And yet, and yet!
憎まれ口 叩きまくり
I keep saying spiteful things,
ひとりになって落ち込んで
then I get depressed when I'm alone,
枕パンチ！！ だから
and punch my pillow!! So...
マイメロディ マイメロディ
My Melody, My Melody.
本当の気持ち 風になって 結ぶリボン
My true feelings turn into the wind, a ribbon that binds.
マイメロディ 歌えオトメゴコロ
My Melody, sing out, maiden's heart.
来る来る恋 つかまえちゃえ
Love is coming, coming, go and catch it!
Wow wow wow 逃がさないから
Wow wow wow, because I won't let it escape
ここへ来て
Come here
キライじゃない ツライです
I don't hate it, but it's painful
真っ赤にだってなっちゃいます
I'll even turn bright red
女の子って不思議で
Girls are made by mysteries...
作られたの
...you know
とどけ
Deliver it...
マイメロディ
My Melody
星空を越えて
Crossing the starry sky...
君の夢 守るリボン
...the ribbon that protects your dreams
マイメロディ
My Melody...
ハート見つけたなら
...if I find your heart
グルグル巻いちゃうからね
I'll spin it around and around!
Wow wow wow 覚悟しといて
Wow wow wow, be prepared!
嘘じゃない
It's not a lie
オトナじゃない オトメです
I'm not an adult, I'm a young girl
泣いたりだってしちゃいます
I'll even cry and such
女の子って魔法で
Girls are made by magic...
作られたの
...you know
スキスキスー
Like, like, like
フワフワフー
Fluffy, fluffy, fluffy
こんなキモチ メロメロディ
Such feelings, Melo-melody
夢だけど 夢じゃない
It's a dream, yet not a dream
お願いね マイメロディ
Please, My Melody
マイメロディ
My Melody
わー！
Wow!
ということで
And so...
最高級にかわいいのと
"Saikoukyuu ni Kawaii no to,"
一途なシンデレラ
"Ichizu na Cinderella,"
あとオトメロディー
and "Otomelody,"
三曲連続で歌いました！
I sang three songs in a row!
やー、雲が晴れたステージって
Wow, the stage after the clouds clear up...
こうなってるのならねー
...looks like this!
すげーでっけー
It's so huge!
武道館みたいなのならね
It's like the Budokan!
あ、ここ見て、シャンデリアがあるのなら！
Ah, look here, there's a chandelier!
ザ・舞踏会、ダンスするって場所なのならね
It's a place for a ball, for dancing!
あとお城の上の方って
And the top of the castle...
こうなってたんだー
...looked like this!
見て、すごいかわいい
Look, it's so cute!
ほらほらこれ、天窓ちゃん
Look look at this, a skylight!
豪華なのならね
It's so luxurious!
すごい！
Amazing!
あ、待って、ルナ・リバースデーの看板もあるのなら！
Ah, wait, there's even a Luna RebirthDay sign!
今日はルナ・リバースデーだからな
Since today is Luna RebirthDay...
見てみて、すごいかわいい
...look look, it's so cute!
ん？なんだなんだなんだ？
Hm? What's this, what's this?
最高だったよー！
That was the best!
え？
Eh?
ポルパパ？
Pol-papa?
ポルナイトやないかい！
It's Pol-knight!
実はね、姫にはまだ
Actually, Princess...
隠された姿が残されているのです！
...there's still a hidden form left for you!
え？の、の、なんなのなら？
Eh? Wh-wh-what is it?
ポルナイトの魔法で
With the magic of Pol-knight...
そのお姿にしてみせましょう！
...let me show you that form!
えー、なになになになに？
Eh, what what what what?
デデーン！
Ta-da!
わー、すごいかわいい
Wow, it's so cute!
新しいヘアスタイルなのならー！
It's a new hairstyle!
ポルナイトがプレゼントしてくれたのならね
Pol-knight gave it to me as a present!
うわー
Wow!
よし、じゃあこの新しい髪型で
Alright, then with this new hairstyle...
歌っちゃうのならー！
...I'm going to sing!
私を推してくれるのなら
If you will support me,
爆レスをあげる
I'll give you a huge fan service!
ア・ナ・タのアイドル
I'm your idol!
サインはB (チュッ)
The sign is B! (Chu!)
あいつは俺が育てたって
Saying 'That guy was raised by me,'
近い将来 自慢してほしいよ
I want you to brag about it in the near future.
こうしちゃいられない
I can't just be doing this.
君と！君と！今を！
With you! With you! Right now!
楽しまなきゃ
We've gotta enjoy it!
引きこもりも人見知りも
Whether you're a shut-in or shy,
普段と違う顔見せてよ
Show me a side of you that's different from usual.
みんな兄弟 調子どうだい
Everyone's a sibling, how're you doing?
なりふり構わずに
Without caring what you look like!
他人に笑われていても関係ない
It doesn't matter if others are laughing at you.
周りがどうとかこうとか気にしない
Don't worry about what those around you think.
主張強すぎ君のサイリウム
Your glowstick is standing out so much.
たとえ世界が私を拒んで
Even if the world rejects me,
ひとりぼっちを感じたとしても
And even if I feel all alone...
アナタが味方でいてくれたら
If you're on my side,
怖いものはないよ
I have nothing to fear!
見てよ 見てよ 何か始まる
Look, look! Something is starting.
君との物語が
Our story is beginning.
ああ なんて素晴らしい景色だ
Ah, what a wonderful sight!
誰が居ようが居まいが関係ない
It doesn't matter who's here or not.
会場が大きい小さいとか気にしない
I don't care if the venue is big or small.
ちゃんと見えてる君のサイリウム
I can see your glowstick perfectly.
今はフッと吹けば飛ぶような
Right now, I'm like something fragile,
小さな小さな才能だけど
A tiny, tiny talent, but...
私を推してくれるのなら
If you will support me...
アナタが味方でいてくれたら
If you're on my side,
爆レスをあげる
I'll give you a huge fan service!
ア・ナ・タのアイドル
I'm your idol!
サインはB (チュッ)
The sign is B! (Chu!)
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない
I won't let a romance scandal get away,
消してあげる
I'll make it disappear for you.
宣誓！私が大統領になったら
I declare! When I become the president,
人の男にちょっかいかける女は島流しにします
I'll exile any woman who flirts with other men!
宣誓！私が大統領になったら
I declare! When I become the president,
いやただの友達だよ～ってごまかす奴はヘソから電気を流します
Those who lie saying 'We're just friends' will be shocked!
だ、だ、だ、大胆不敵
F-f-f-fearless!
センセーショナルクローズアップ
Sensational close-up!
D, D, D, Don't cry
やるぜ徹底的にリサーチだ
I'll do some thorough research!
大嫌い？ しょうがない？
You hate me? Can't be helped?
クズは病気ね バイバイバイ
Being trash is a disease, bye-bye-bye!
権力！財産！地位名声！！
Power! Wealth! Status and fame!!
なんにもないけど裁きたいでしょ？
I have none, but you want to judge, right?
だ、だ、だ、大統領になったらね
When I become the president,
まずは君を捕まえるね
I'll catch you first,
濡れたタオルで 洗いざらい吐かせるね
And make you spit out everything with a wet towel!
誰ですか あの女
Who is that woman?
ダメですか そうですか
Is it no good? I see.
ロマンスの不祥事 逃がさない
I won't let a romance scandal get away,
消してあげる
I'll make it disappear for you.
しる・ヴ・ぷれぷれ ぷれぜぜんと
Sil-vous-pre-pre president!
宣誓！私が大統領になったら
I declare! When I become the president,
ただの仕事の付き合いだよ～って言う奴は二度と働けなくしてやります
Those who say 'It's for work' will never work again!
宣誓！以下略！
I declare! Et cetera!
いや向こうが強引でさ～っていう男の口にはレジンを流し込んで固めてやります
For 'pushy' men, I'll harden their mouths with resin!
まるでドン・ファン気取りスキャンダラス
Like a scandalous self-proclaimed Don Juan.
ま、ま、ま、末端価格 甲斐性なしのスクープね
F-f-f-final price, a scoop about a good-for-nothing!
愛はない？理由じゃない
No love? That's no excuse.
悪くないのに はいはいはい
You're not at fault? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
軽薄！のうのう！厚顔無恥！！
Frivolous! Carefree! Shameless!!
なんにもないとかありえないでしょ？
Saying you have nothing is impossible, right?
だ、だ、だ、大統領になってもね
Even if I become the president,
たぶん君は変わらないね
You probably won't change.
しらっととぼけて
With a blank face and playing dumb,
のらりくらりかわすのね
You'll dodge me elusively.
デートですか こんばんは
A date? Good evening.
本気ですか そうですか
Are you serious? I see.
情熱とは不注意 微熱も
Passion is carelessness, even a slight fever,
消してしまいたい
I want to erase it all.
ワン・ツー・スリー
One, two, three
だだだ、大胆不敵センス
Da da da, reckless sense
大統領になったらマジで君を捕まえるね
Once I become president, I'll seriously catch you, okay?
濡れたタオルで
With a wet towel
粗相の不祥事も汚名返上ね
I'll make you erase even the signs of your wrongdoing
(ど・ど・ど！)
(Do do do!)
どこですか 今あんた
Where are you now?
見っけちゃった バレちゃった
I caught you, I exposed you
夜道にはご用心 さよなら
Beware of the night roads, goodbye
代わりに歓声
In place of the cheers
シル・ヴ・プレプレ プレジデント
S'il vous president, hip hip hooray president
あなた今も忘れたいこと
The things you still want to forget
悲しいこと
The sad things
あるのかしらね
I wonder if you have any
知らない映画なのに涙を流すのは
Shedding tears even though it's a movie I don't know
ドラマチックが足りてないからよ
Because there's not enough drama
そんな風にもつかないこと
Things that don't even seem like that
くだらないこと
Worthless things
考えてばかりね
You're always thinking about them
雨が上がれば相も変わらず
When the rain stops, just like always
行く顔も誰かのものになるのでしょう
The passing faces will probably become someone else's too
突発のファンタジーも全部
Even sudden fantasies, all of them
愛の為よ
Are for the sake of love
なんて一体全体どうしてどうして何故何故ハテナ
Like, what on earth, why, why, why, why, question mark?
不安定な勝手な どこまで行くの
Unstable, selfish, how far will it go?
あなた一切合切放り出しても
Even if you throw everything away
冗談じゃないないわ
It's no joke, no
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendez-vous
その時がきたってどうにもならないぜ
Even when that time comes, it's no use
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリーするだけ
Vague truths only make me feel melancholy
あたし今重なっています イエス
I am overlapping now, yes
イエス
Yes
あー全然おかしなハートばかり
Ah, nothing but strange hearts
食指がピクトもしないわ
My appetite doesn't even twitch
実体のない感情放っておいたって
Even if I leave my insubstantial emotions alone
策略なんてありやせんのに何故
There's no strategy involved, so why?
あーもうこれきりよ
Ah, this is the end of it
あたしの勝手なキスもじっとこらえて
Enduring even my selfish kisses
とりあえず限界点
For now, the limit point
年中無休のリップサービス
24/7 lip service
等閑かましては平気
Neglecting it and being fine
どーかなっちゃう昼下がりは
Early afternoons where things go wrong
涙の目にも二木
Futaki even in teary eyes
今やたまのミュージックのせいで
Now, because of the music of Tama
あなたの話は一向に聞き取れない
I can't hear what you're saying at all
少しはまとなこと言って イェ
Say something a bit more sensible, yeah
回り出したターンテーブルで全部
On the spinning turntable, all of it
忘れさせてよ
Let me forget
だけど一体全体どうしてどうして何故何故ハテナ
But what on earth, why, why, why, why, question mark?
不透明な勝手な 消えないままで
Opaque, selfish, remaining without disappearing
あなた一向に噛み合ってなくても
Even if you're not in sync at all
冗談じゃないないわ
It's no joke, no
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendez-vous
その時がきたってどうにもならないぜ
Even when that time comes, it's no use
不甲斐ないわ 感情なんて後回しで
It's pathetic, leaving emotions for later
踊りだすだけ あたしと重なっている街
Just starting to dance, the city overlapping with me
イエス
Yes
冗談じゃないないわ
It's no joke, no
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendez-vous
その時がきたってどうにもならないぜ
Even when that time comes, it's no use
不甲斐ないわ 感情なんて後回しで
It's pathetic, leaving emotions for later
踊り出すだけ あたしと重なっている街
Just starting to dance, the city overlapping with me
アイアイヤー
Ai ai ya
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendez-vous
その時がきたってどうにもならないぜ
Even when that time comes, it's no use
曖昧な本当なんてメランコリーするだけ
Vague truths only make me feel melancholy
あたし今重なっています イエス
I am overlapping now, yes
イエス
Yes
二酸化炭素を吐き出して
Exhaling carbon dioxide
あの子が呼吸をしているよ
That girl is breathing
どん天模様の空の下
Under the cloudy sky
つぼみのままでゆれながら
Swaying while still a bud
野良犬は僕の骨くわえ
The stray dog bites my bone
野生の力をためしてる
Testing its wild power
路地裏に月がおっこちて
The moon fell into the back alley
犬の目玉は四角だよ
The dog's eyes are square
今日 人類がはじめて
Today, for the first time, humanity...
木星についたよ
reached Jupiter
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus...
近づいたんだよ
has drawn near
アラビアの笛の音響く
The sound of Arabian flutes echoes
町のはずれの夢の跡
At the edge of town, the ruins of dreams
翼をなくしたペガサスが
A Pegasus that lost its wings
夜空にハシゴかけている
Is leaning a ladder against the night sky
武器を担いだ兵隊さん
A soldier carrying a weapon
南に行こうとしてるけど
Is trying to go south, but
サーベルの音はチャラチャラと
The sound of his saber clinks and clanks
街の空気を汚してる
Polluting the city air
今日 人類が初めて
Today, for the first time,
木星についたよ
humanity reached Jupiter
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus
近づいたんだよ
is drawing near too
歌を忘れたカナリア
A canary that forgot its song
牛を忘れた牛小屋
A cowshed that forgot its cows
こわれた磁石を拾い集める
Gathering up broken magnets,
博士はまるはげさ
the professor is stone-bald
あの子は花火を打ち上げて
That child set off fireworks,
この日が来たの祝ってる
celebrating that this day has come
冬の花火は強すぎて
The winter fireworks were too strong,
ぼくらの体は砕け散る
and our bodies shattered to pieces
ブーゲンビリアの木の下で
Under the bougainvillea tree,
ぼくはあの子を捜すけど
I look for that child, but
月の光に邪魔されて
getting in the way of the moonlight,
あの子のかけらは見つからない
I can't find any pieces of that child
今日 人類が初めて
Today, for the first time,
木星についたよ
humanity reached Jupiter
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus
近づいたんだよ
is drawing near too
今日 人類が初めて
Today, for the first time,
木星についたよ
humanity reached Jupiter
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus
近づいたんだよ
is drawing near too
さるにはなりたくない
I don't want to become a monkey
こわれた磁石を砂浜で
Picking up broken magnets,
ひろっているだけさ
just picking them up on the beach
今日 人類が初めて
Today, for the first time,
木星についたよ
humanity reached Jupiter
ピテカントロプスになる日も
The day we become Pithecanthropus
近づいたんだよ
is drawing near too
さよならよ
Goodbye...
さよならな
朝まで踊る 夢だけ見せて
Let me dream only of dancing until morning
時計の鐘が鳴る魔法
The magic of the clock's chime
曖昧な指 誘う階段
Vague fingers, an inviting staircase
三段飛ばしに跳ねていく
I leap up, skipping three steps at a time
馬車の中で震えてた
I was trembling inside the carriage
みじめな古着 めくりめくれよ
Tear away these miserable old clothes
夜の舞踏
In this night's ball
見知らぬ 顔探す
Searching for an unfamiliar face
囁くあの声が
That whispering voice...
握り締めた刃
Grips the blade tight
突き立て
And plunges it
すべてを奪えと
Commanding to take everything away
孤児 集う城
A castle where orphans gather
笑み仮面に描いて
Drawing a smile on a mask
偽りの慈しみさえ
Even false compassion...
羽で包む
Is wrapped in wings
熾天使
By a seraph
灰の中で
Within the ashes
赤く溶けて
Melting red
混じる
Mixing together
硝子の靴
The glass slipper
今更見る
Looking at it now
震えているの
I'm trembling
あなたが目をやる時計
The clock you cast your eyes upon
靴脱ぎ踊るの
Taking off shoes and dancing
スロープ抜けて
Passing through the slope
爪先まで伸びる
Stretching to the tips of my toes
指差し
Pointing my finger
すくう雫
Scooping up droplets
口づけて
Pressing our lips together
走る衝動
A racing impulse
背骨抜けていく
Passing through my spine
刹那
In a fleeting moment
鐘は 鳴らさないで
Please don't let the bells ring
あなたにひざまずき
Kneeling before you
まだダメと叫んだ
I screamed, "Not yet!"
右手が
My right hand...
突き刺すサヨナラ
Stabs a goodbye
消せない硝煙を
Unforgettable gunpowder smoke...
香水にまとう姫
The princess cloaked in perfume
強い瞳 僕の凍った
Strong eyes, my frozen...
仮面ごと打ち抜く
Piercing right through the mask
今も耳にあなたの吐息が
Your breath still lingers in my ears
突き刺さるの遠い夢
Stabbing through a distant dream
ステンドグラスごし光る月が
The moon shining through the stained glass
君にかぶせたベール
Is a veil cast over you
ドレス膝で裂いて
Tearing my dress at the knee
ティアラは投げ捨てて
Throwing my tiara away
見つめあう瞳と瞳が
Our eyes meet, gazing into each other
火花を放つ
As sparks fly
孤独な魂が
Our lonely souls
炎あげ惹かれあう
Are drawn together in flames
その涙すくえないなら
If I can't catch those tears...
まるで一人遊び
It's just like playing alone
時よ止まれ今は
Time, please stop for now
あなたに酔いしれて
Intoxicated by you
揺れる鼓動一つ一つを
Every single beat of my racing heart...
刻みつけたい
I want to engrave them
とどまれ熱く濡れ
Stay here, hot and wet
打ち付ける高まりに
In this pounding surge
これ以上は動けないよ
I can't move anymore
まるで御伽話
It's just like a fairy tale
みんな！ここからは大事な告知タイムなのらな！イェーイ！
Everyone! From here, it's time for some important announcements! Yay!
ポポ、ポポはそこで見ててなのらね。イェーイ！
Popo, you watch from there, okay? Yay!
では、まずはこちら！デデン！
Now, first is this! Ta-da!
姫森ルーナ 誕生日記念 2025のグッズが出てます！イェーイ！
Himemori Luna Birthday Celebration 2025 merchandise is out now! Yay!
ではね、こちら詳細見ていきましょう。デデン！
Now then, let's take a look at the details. Ta-da!
ふたりのルーナ♡アクリルジオラマスタンドなのらな！
The "Two Lunas♡Acrylic Diorama Stand" nanora!
イラストはソイル先生に描いていただきました。
The illustration was drawn by Soil-sensei.
前のね、髪型と今回のルーナのね、新しい髪型のルーナが、
The previous hairstyle and Luna's new hairstyle for this event...
そして今回の生誕ライブのステージに登場しました。
...have appeared on the stage of this birthday live.
こちらはね、立体的なパーツが華やかな可愛い素敵な豪華仕様のジオラマスタンドになっております。
This is a diorama stand with a gorgeous, cute, and wonderful luxury design with 3D parts.
そして、次はこちら。デデン！
And next is this. Ta-da!
姫森ルーナぬいぐるみ 守ってルーナイトver.
The Himemori Luna Plushie: Protect me LuKnight ver.!
届きました！
It's here!
守ってルーナイトの衣装のんなたんが
Luna-tan in her 'Mamotte Knight' outfit...
ぬいぐるみに なりました！
...has been turned into a plushie!
ぜひぜひ、みんなおうちに お迎えして
Please, everyone, take her home with you...
んなたんをね 守ってほしいのらよ！
...and protect Luna-tan, okay?
そして、次はこちら！ デデン！
And next is this! Ta-da!
ルーナイト2wayバッグ！
Luna Knight 2-way Bag!
さっきのぬいぐるみも すっぽり入ってしまう
The plushie from before fits perfectly inside!
ルーナイトがアピールできる バッグになたにます
It's a bag that lets you show off your Luna Knight pride!
バッグはね、なんと リュックにもなって超便利！
The bag can even become a backpack, so it's super handy!
デザインに使用されているモチーフは
The motifs used in the design...
ルーナイト由来のもので統一しているので
...are all unified with Luna Knight themes.
バッグモードでも リュックモードでも
Whether in bag mode or backpack mode,
お好きな方で使ってください
please use it whichever way you like!
次はこちら！ デデン！
Next is this! Ta-da!
ルーナイトカードホルダー！
Luna Knight Card Holder!
ルーナイト型のカードホルダーです
It's a card holder shaped like a Luna Knight!
チェキ風カードや ホロカのカードも入れられちゃうので
You can fit cheki-style cards or Holocards inside,
んなたんのみんなは こっちもしっかり守ってくださいね
so everyone, please protect your cards with this!
そして次はこちら！ デデン！
And next is this! Ta-da!
ASMRボイス 『舞踏会の帰り道』
ASMR Voice: 'The Way Home from the Ball'
今回はね、舞踏会をイメージした 生誕祭ライブなので
Since this birthday live has a ball theme,
ルーナたんと帰路についた ひとときをボイスにしました
I made a voice drama about a moment on the way home with Luna-tan!
馬車の中という密室で
Inside the private space of a carriage...
なんか急接近とかあっちゃうかも？
...maybe we'll get a little closer?
ということで、最後に改めて フルセットを見てみましょう！
So, let's take one last look at the full set!
こちら、フルセット購入特典は… デデン！
The bonus for purchasing the full set is... Ta-da!
オリジナルカード！
Original Card!
イラストはジョイネット先生で
The illustration is by Joynet-sensei,
表面がチェキ風のカードになってます
and the front side is a cheki-style card.
裏面は招待状風のデザインに なっていておしゃれなのら！
The back has an invitation-style design and it's so stylish!
そして、通常バージョンの フルセット購入特典は
And the bonus for the standard version full set is...
箔押し複製サイン入り チェキ風ブロマイドカード！
...a cheki-style bromide card with a foil-stamped signature!
そして、数量限定バージョンの フルセット購入特典は
And the bonus for the limited quantity version full set is...
直筆サイン入り チェキ風ブロマイドカードなならら！
...a cheki-style bromide card with a handwritten signature!
みんな、ゲットしてほしいのら！
Everyone, I hope you'll get one!
グッズはね、配信終了後 販売開始です！
The goods will go on sale after the stream ends!
そしてそして、もう一つ 大事なお知らせがあります
And one more thing, I have another important announcement.
こちら！ 「んなっしょいぱっしょん」！
This! 'Nnashoi Passion'!
こちらをね、このあと 歌わせていただきます
I'll be singing this song right after this!
みんな大好きな 「んなっしょい」って言葉 使っているのでね
It uses the word 'Nnashoi' that everyone loves,
みんなこのあと いっぱいんなっしょいしな！
so everyone, do lots of 'Nnashoi' later!
この配信が終わったら MVも公開されます！
The MV will also be released after this stream ends!
そしてMV公開後、メン限が 今回初めてやることになったので
And after the MV release, I'll be doing my first membership-only stream!
こちらもお楽しみに！
Please look forward to that too!
ではね、歌います！ んなっしょいぱっしょん！
Now then, I'll sing! Nnashoi Passion!
んん… んん… んない… 泣きたい
Nn... Nn... Nnai... I want to cry
別にオチとかねぇのら！
It's not like there's a punchline!
むにゃむにゃ目をこする
Mumble mumble, rubbing my eyes
囚われた城に
In the captive castle,
パーフェクトな朝
a perfect morning.
おないおないお布団
Bye-bye, bye-bye, futon!
飛び出して海へ行こう
Let's jump out and head to the sea!
神様だって
Even God...
間違うんだって
...makes mistakes.
よくある話だそうです
That's what they say, apparently.
姫様にね
For the Princess,
見とれちゃうんだって
...everyone's captivated.
やれやれなのらね
Good grief, isn't it?
夢を夢見て
Dreaming a dream,
恋に恋して生きていたい
I want to live, in love with love.
だから
So,
これでいいのら！
this is just fine!
んん… んん… んない… 泣きたい
Nn... Nn... Nnai... I want to cry
はらわらいたい
I want to laugh heartily
心だってうらら
Even my heart is bright
変えるのら！
I'll change it!
だから会いたい
So I want to see you
その願いに
To that wish...
いま約束の
...now, the promised...
合言葉
...password.
いくよっ
Here we go!
んなっしょい！！
Nnashoi!!
まどろみも
Drowsiness,
ホラーな夜もあるけど
and even scary nights...
でもね
But you know,
んなっしょい！！
Nnashoi!!
いつまでもみんな
Everyone, forever,
おりゅからへいき
I'm okay because you're here
まだ遊び足りねぇのら！
I still haven't played enough!
んなっしょいぱっしょん
Nnasshoi Passion
くないくない 夜の中
In the never-ending night
ティアラを外して 城を抜けたら
Taking off my tiara and leaving the castle
深い深い 海に出れば
Heading out into the deep, deep sea
...バレてんのら グッドナイト
...It's been found out, good night
姫様はね わがまま〜なんて
They say the Princess is selfish
おとぎ話 そうでしょ？
A fairy tale, isn't it?
何がなんだって わたしなんだって
No matter what, I am who I am
これでいいのら
This is fine
なりたい わたしでいたい！
I want to be, I want to stay as myself!
どこへだって向かってゆけるのなら
If I can head anywhere
ならば さぁない
Then there's no choice
この思いに
To this feeling
今 許される合言葉
A password allowed now
いくよっ！ なんそい！！
Let's go! Nnasshoi!!
サンゴ礁 白い砂浜も綺麗
Coral reefs, white sandy beaches are also beautiful
そこに なんそい！！
There, Nnasshoi!!
輝くわたし
A shining me
Q. 帰る理由は？
Q. The reason for returning?
A. そこになければねのら！
A. If it's not there, then there's no reason!
んなあああぁい！
Nnaaaaai!
リピート アフター ミー
Repeat after me
なんそい！！ なんそい！！
Nnasshoi!! Nnasshoi!!
せーの
Ready, go!
なんそい！！ なんそい！！
Nnasshoi!! Nnasshoi!!
もう１回！
One more time!
なんそい！！ なんそい！！
Nnasshoi!! Nnasshoi!!
いいええ
Nice!
熱い視線が集中
Hot gazes are focused
ハラハラする心にムガムチュウ
Absorbed in the heart that flutters
だから… だから…
Because... because...
これでいいのら
This is fine
泣きたい から笑いたい
I want to cry, so I want to laugh
心だって奪ってあげるのら！
I'll steal your heart, you know!
だから会いたい その願いに
Because I want to meet you, on that wish
今 約束の合言葉
A promised password now
いくよ！ なんそい！！
Let's go! Nnasshoi!!
まどろみも ホラーな夜もあるけれど
Even the drowsy, scary nights exist, but
でもね！ なんそい！！
But you know! Nnasshoi!!
この先も みんな
Everyone, from here on too
おりからへいき
It's okay to start over
まだ遊び足りねぇのら！
I haven't played enough yet!
出演
Cast
姫森ルーナ
Himemori Luna
尾丸ポルカ（ポル〜ナイト）
Omaru Polka (Polu~night)
ルーナイト
Lu-Knight
生誕ライブ見に来てくれてありがとうなのら...。
Thank you for coming to watch my birthday live...
今年は体調不良の時期だったからまともに出せなかったかもしれない...。
Since I was feeling unwell this year, I might not have been able to give it my all...
でも最後まで頑張ったのら！！ぷりいぬ！！
But I did my best until the end, even in Toy!! Puri-inu!!
これからもずっとずっと姫様になる夢を応援してね！
Please keep supporting my dream of becoming a Princess forever!
I love you ちゅぱちゅぱ... 2025.10.10 るーななのらー
I love you, chupa-chupa... 2025.10.10 It's Luna-nora~
CH4NGE
Original: Giga / Cover: Amane Kanata
とべ、起こせ！ 狙うは事故
Fly, make a move! Aiming for a crash
一世一代さあ何賭す？
Once in a lifetime, come on, what will you bet?
自問自答
Self-questioning
勝つか負けるか
Will I win or will I lose?
ドローなんてないわ
There's no such thing as a draw
幕開けるわ
The curtain is rising
カッチンして ラッキーマニー
Click it and make some lucky money
どっちもむりー…
Both are impossible, huh?
Cigar Cigar
引けるか否か 自分次第だな
Can I pull it off or not? It's up to me
余裕で！ 振り切り全BETだぜいイェイ☆
Easy! Full swing, going all in, yeah!
そこどけ！
Get out of the way!